We came to Costco to get Kimchi.
Kelly. Yeah.
So a stranger asked me what Kimchi is.
Yeah.
Does it happen to you often in Costco too?
Maybe not ask.
I mean, I've had a few people ask what it is,
but also then just
I feel like I've had many conversations start
because I'm buying Kimchi or looking at it or something.
At Costco, it's happened quite a few times.
Like the one lady said
she's tried it before,
but it's way too spicy for her.
I had another guy randomly stop me in the grocery store to ask what people use Napa cabbages for,
which I thought was really random.
And he was just lucky
I knew At least, from a Korean standpoint, what it gets used for.
But yeah, it does happen.
So what is the best description for Kimchi to people in here?
I'd say it's fermented cabbage. Korean fermented cabbage.
where I worked, I got introduced to a restaurant, a Kimchi Jjigae restaurant, by my coworkers,
and we used to go there all the time.
Like, we probably as a group would go there once a week, every other week or so,
but if there was ever times where I really wanted it, and no one could go with me, I went by myself,
because it was just... In the buildings right next to where we worked,
so it was very close and easy to get to.
So the people who worked there obviously knew us very well.
Especially when I would go by myself.
I mean, all of us as a group of foreigners kind of got stared at.
But when I'd go by myself, people were really shocked.
So I had my meal paid for at least two times, I think, while I was there.
Because they were always different Koreans, usually older,
and they'd come in and then be shocked to see a foreigner sitting down to eat Kimchi jjigae.
So yeah, so I had my meal paid for. They bought it at least two times, I think.
Kelly.
Did you expect that you'd have Kimchi jjigae this often in the USA?
No, I did not.
But I feel like I kind of encouraged it by giving you a 10 out of 10 on that one soup you made.
And unfortunately, some of them have been good, but none of them have quite lived up to that one you made.
I was introduced to the Kimchi Jjigae restaurant by my coworkers.
And I can't say like really why it was so good, but I just know that I really liked it,
and we went all the time.
And it basically made it where, to me,
that style of kimchi jjigae
so we would always put ramen in it
it always had like the... i can never pronounce it correctly the Tteok(rice cake)
and then we always got the egg rolls with it
i don't know that just that always made it to me that that is what kimchi jjigae is supposed to taste like
So everything else just didn't taste the same
because that to me was what kimchi jjigae tasted like.
But I don't even know, technically, was it really that good of one? I mean, probably not.
It's probably not that healthy of a one,
but like that just to me was,
the flavor of it was delicious.
And that's what I always based it off of.
And unfortunately, like your mom started cooking kimchi jjigae,
to me, it was just a completely different taste to what I liked from that restaurant.
It's definitely better than the last one you made.
It's still not as good as that very first one, that you made two months ago.
Maybe because I haven't cooked kimchi jjigae for like six weeks, seven weeks.
Maybe it just tasted so good?
Yeah, it could be.
So, you didn't give me the answer,
the score for me.
Oh, sorry. Mmm.
Seven?
It's a passing score.
The problem is you don't follow a recipe, so every time you never know how it's going to turn out,
how much, of one thing you put too much and it changes the flavor.
I don't know,
something about these ones feel oilier to me,
like a thicker oilier.
Whereas I feel like that one didn't have that oiliness to it.
so that'll be what you have to do
let's take a two month break from kimchi jjigae and then you cook it again
we'll test it
Hajoon!
who do you love?
Rowan, love? Who?
Really? Who else?
Baby?
Who else?